A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3 FA388
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Tanzania, 1966-1995; 723; 16 Box(es)
  - Tanzania - Social Sciences, 723.S
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Scholarships Workshop - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Secondary Education in Tanzania, 1985, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Social Sciences - Staff Training, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Social Sciences - Staff Training, 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Sociology (I), 1973-1975, 1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Sociology (II), 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Sociology (II), 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Sociology (II), 1977-1978, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Sociology - Evaluation, 1974, 1976, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Sociology - Staff Development, 1973-1974, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (I), 1974-1975, 1978-1982 (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (II), 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (II), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (II), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (II), 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (II), 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Staff Development (II), 1982-1983, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Tanzanian Economy, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Tanzanian Economy - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Wright, Marcia (I), 1974, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - University of Dar es Salaam - Wright, Marcia (II), 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 216)